University of Connecticut 1998.0185
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series II: Subject Files, 1935-1962
  - Regulations & Policies
    - Communism, 1953 (Box 35:, Folder 29)
    - Concessions and soliciting policy, 1948 (Box 36:, Folder 1)
    - Discrimination in fraternities - resolution, 1949 (Box 36:, Folder 2)
    - Establishment of a university branch (Box 36:, Folder 3)
    - Exchange of students and professional Personnel act, 1949 (Box 36:, Folder 4)
    - Firearms on campus policy, 1952 (Box 36:, Folder 5)
    - General statements on university (Box 36:, Folder 6)
    - Graduate assistantships policy, 1952 (Box 36:, Folder 7)
    - Grievance procedure classified employees, 1949 (Box 36:, Folder 8)
    - Higher education in Connecticut (Box 36:, Folder 9)
    - Higher education, national defense, and Public policy, 1950 (Box 36:, Folder 10)
    - Infirmary policy, 1949 (Box 36:, Folder 11)
    - Lease form, business development and house lots, 1949 (Box 36:, Folder 12)
    - Leaves of absence, policy for members of Professional staff, 1953 November 3 (Box 36:, Folder 13)
    - Livestock quotas, 1954 April 23 (Box 36:, Folder 14)
    - Medical, dental and veterinary schools (Box 36:, Folder 15)
    - Military training, regarding compulsory, 1935 (Box 36:, Folder 16)
    - Organization chart of the university, 1935 (Box 36:, Folder 17)
    - Pharmacy, program in hospital pharmacy, 1953 (Box 36:, Folder 18)
    - Public relations policy, 1954 (Box 36:, Folder 19)
    - Publications board, mimeograph material, 1954 (Box 36:, Folder 20)
    - Radio isotopes and other sources of ionizing Radiation, regulations (Box 36:, Folder 21)
    - Regional cooperation among New England state universities, state of policies, 1958 (Box 36:, Folder 22)
    - Research grants, schedule (Box 36:, Folder 23)
    - Research titles, 1953 (Box 36:, Folder 24)
    - Residence policy, 1958 January 15 (Box 36:, Folder 25)
    - Religious education (Box 36:, Folder 26)
    - Research Foundation, 1956 (Box 36:, Folder 27)
    - Retirement contributions, summer session and extension teaching (Box 36:, Folder 28)
    - ROTC policy, 1951 (Box 36:, Folder 29)
    - Room reservation policy, use of university Facilities, 1953 (Box 36:, Folder 30)
    - Sale of agricultural products policy, 1954 April 23 (Box 36:, Folder 31)
    - Scholarships and financial aid policy (Box 36:, Folder 32)
    - Self-supporting activities fund (Box 36:, Folder 33)
    - Smoking in buildings, policy (Box 36:, Folder 34)
    - Social security for state institutions, 1952 (Box 36:, Folder 35)
    - State university (Box 36:, Folder 36)
    - Student attendance at classes, admission standards, scholastic morality (Box 36:, Folder 37)
    - Student organizations, university policy, 1947 (Box 36:, Folder 38)
    - Teaching loads policy (Box 37:, Folder 39)
    - Ticket policy (Box 37:, Folder 40)
    - Travel policy (Box 37:, Folder 41)
    - Trends in organization and coordination in higher education (Box 37:, Folder 42)
    - Use of von der Mehden Recital Hall (Box 37:, Folder 43)
  - 75th Anniversary
    - Correspondence (Box 37:, Folder 44)
      - Anniversary budget (Box 37:, Folder 45)
      - Student representatives (Box 37:, Folder 46)
      - Prospective speakers (Box 37:, Folder 47)
      - Film production (Box 37:, Folder 48)
      - Anniversary medallion (Box 37:, Folder 49)
      - Anniversary certificates (Box 37:, Folder 50)
      - Thank you letters (Box 37:, Folder 51)
      - General (Box 37:, Folder 52)
    - Honors day convocation, 1957 May 11 (Box 37:, Folder 53)
    - Programs and Publicity (Box 37:, Folder 54)
    - Speeches (Box 37:, Folder 55)
    - 75th Anniversary committee (Box 37:, Folder 56)
    - Budget, general expenses (Box 37:, Folder 57)
  - Jorgensen Speeches
    - The business teacher as a philosopher technician (Box 37:, Folder 58)
    - The future of the university (Box 37:, Folder 59)
    - Connecticut farm forum - radio interview (Box 37:, Folder 60)
    - New York State educational conference (Box 37:, Folder 61)
    - A critique of American education (Box 37:, Folder 62)
    - On the occasion of the dedication of the Storrs Community Church (Box 37:, Folder 63)
    - The educationist as a social engineer (Box 37:, Folder 64)
    - Problems of college admission at the Connecticut State College (Box 37:, Folder 65)
    - Conovation address (Box 37:, Folder 66)
    - In observing Armistice Day (Box 37:, Folder 67)
    - Education and Youth (Box 37:, Folder 68)
    - Notes, State Chamber of Commerce address (Box 37:, Folder 69)
    - The youth problem of Connecticut (Box 37:, Folder 70)
    - [Alumni] (Box 37:, Folder 71)
    - Radio Address, Connecticut Technical Council (Box 37:, Folder 72)
    - Opening Convocation, 1934 September 20 (Box 37:, Folder 73)
    - Convocation address, 1935 November 7; (2 copies) (Box 37:, Folder 74)
    - Youth conservation, 1936 February 20 (Box 37:, Folder 75)
    - Youth and higher education, 1937 February 22 (Box 37:, Folder 76)
    - Commencement, 1937 (Box 37:, Folder 77)
    - Convocation, 1937 September (Box 37:, Folder 78)
    - Installation of President George H. Shafer, Willimantic State Teachers College, 1937 September 27 (Box 37:, Folder 79)
    - The unadjusted child in the school room, 1937 October (Box 37:, Folder 80)
    - Staff meeting, 1937 October 7 (Box 37:, Folder 81)
    - Education and democracy, 1937 November 8 (Box 37:, Folder 82)
    - Is teaching a profession?, 1937 December 7 (Box 37:, Folder 83)
    - Values in college athletics. MA State College, 1937 December 9 (Box 38:, Folder 1)
    - The responsibility of the State College to Connecticut Agriculture, 1937 December 16 (Box 38:, Folder 2)
    - Education and industry in New England, 1938 March 15 (Box 38:, Folder 3)
    - High school commencement address, 1938 June (Box 38:, Folder 4)
    - Individual worth and the sanction of reason, 1938 June 12 (Box 38:, Folder 5)
    - Opening convocation, 1938 September 27 (Box 38:, Folder 6)
    - Do it the hard way. Commencement address, 1939 Jun (Box 38:, Folder 7)
    - Opening convocation, 1939 September 25 (Box 38:, Folder 8)
    - CT hall of fame. Radio broadcast, 1939 December 31 (Box 38:, Folder 9)
    - To foster and perpetuate a 100% Americanism, 1940 April 16 (Box 38:, Folder 10)
    - Interdependence of agriculture and industry, 1940 May 28 (Box 38:, Folder 11)
    - Annual extension conference, 1940 June 4 - 6 (Box 38:, Folder 12)
    - Civilization at the crossroads, 1940 June (Box 38:, Folder 13)
    - Opening convocation, 1940 September 18 (Box 38:, Folder 14)
    - The issue of war and peace. Commencement Address, 1941 June 8 (Box 38:, Folder 15)
    - Responsibility for peace. Opening Convocation, 1941 September 18 (Box 38:, Folder 16)
    - What the University of Connecticut expects of the farmers, 1942 January 8 (Box 38:, Folder 17)
    - Notes. Student meeting, 1942 January 9 (Box 38:, Folder 18)
    - The need for unity of purpose and effort, 1942 February 20 (Box 38:, Folder 19)
    - Dedication of Hurley Hall. Cheshire Academy, 1942 May 9 (Box 38:, Folder 20)
    - Dedication of buildings, 1942 May 17 (Box 38:, Folder 21)
    - The Authority of the liberated yet disciplined mind, 1942 (Box 38:, Folder 22)
      Scope and Contents note
      (Commencement)
    - Opening convocation, 1942 September 24 (Box 38:, Folder 23)
    - Military commencement, 1943 May 17 (Box 38:, Folder 24)
    - Victory and the future. Commencement, 1943 May 30 (Box 38:, Folder 25)
    - Opening convocation, 1944 September 22 (Box 38:, Folder 26)
    - Opening convocation, 1947 September 26 (Box 38:, Folder 27)
    - The challenge of commencement day, 1953 (Box 38:, Folder 28)
    - Education and the world community, 1959 February 23 (Box 38:, Folder 29)